solidsignal.com 2009-05-05

# Privacy Policy | Solid Signal

---|---  
**Solid Signal Privacy Policy**  
   
Effective Date: March 28, 2009  
**Online Privacy**  
We've all heard about it, we're all concerned about it: Online Privacy! But just what is Online Privacy? At Solid Signal, we believe that the issues of online privacy and security go far beyond simply protecting customer credit card numbers from hackers, and not SPAM mailing our customers. We strongly believe that the privacy policy and associated practices of a company reveal the true character of that company.  
We hope that you find this document helpful and informative, if you have any questions regarding what is contained within it, please don't hesitate to send us an email to  _[ info@SolidSignal.com](mailto:info@SolidSignal.com)_.   
**Scope of the Policy**  
**Signal Group, LLC** is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program.  TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices.  This privacy statement covers the sites ** [ http://www.solidsignal.tv/](http://www.solidsignal.tv/) **and **  http://www.solidsignal.com/.**  Because Signal Group wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Matt Faul at  [ info@solidsignal.com](mailto:info@solidsignal.com) ****.  If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact TRUSTe at [ http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.  
Please note also that although some of Solid Signal's products are only sold to residents of the Unites States, our practice of protecting your privacy knows no borders. If you are an international visitor or customer and you share your information with us, you too can be assured that our general protection policy will apply equally to that information. Signal Groups privacy policy and its protection of personally identifiable information applies to ALL VISITORS, acting in any capacity whatsoever.  
**The Information We Collect**  
Your privacy is extremely important to us. In the normal operation of our business we collect personal information about you. This statement is a full and complete disclosure about the information we collect and how it might be used. This notice of disclosure regarding our information collection policy applies to all information collected or submitted on any Solid Signal websites as identified above. Solid Signal (Signal Group LLC) is the sole owner of information collected on our websites. We do not sell, rent or share this information in ways that are different from what is disclosed in this statement.  
**IP Addresses and Header Information**  
A Web cookie, is a parcel of text sent by a server to a web browser and then sent back unchanged by the browser each time it accesses that server. HTTP cookies are used for authenticating, tracking, and maintaining specific information about users, such as site preferences and the contents of their electronic shopping carts. The cookie that is tracked is not tied to your personally identifiable information.  
We log information site-wide regarding visitor IP addresses. This information is contained in the HTTP Header and is passed to us each time you request a page or image from one of our sites. It is essentially your address, and lets us know where to send the page or image that was requested. This address does not track any personal information and is reset when you restart your browser.  
There is no personal information gathered by us, or passed to us by the HTTP header.   
**Personal Information (About You)**  
Solid Signal collects personally identifiable information (PII) about consumers in a variety of ways:   
**·** Through a variety of response forms and email links on its websites. Such as when you register for an account, "contact us" or using our "tell a friend" feature. These resources help you get in touch with us for a variety of reasons. In the case of response forms, fields not critical to the processing of the form are made 'optional'. You could expect to see the following personally identifiable information collected on one of these forms:   
    º Your name   
    º Your email address   
    º Your telephone number (possibly multiple numbers)   
    º Your zip code   
**·** At the point of sale we collect all information necessary to the processing of the order being placed. Specifically, the Personally Identifiable data we collect is:   
    º Your name   
    º Your email address   
    º Your telephone number (possibly multiple numbers)   
    º Your address (possibly multiple addresses)  
    º Your financial information (such as credit card number)  
**·** Through our newsletter and special offers email sign up, the Personally Identifiable data we collect is:  
     º Your email address  
**·** Through response forms offered to give consumers an opportunity to take part in a variety of contests and incentives. You could expect to see the following personally identifiable information collected on one of these forms:   
    º Your name   
    º Your email address   
    º Your telephone number (possibly multiple numbers)   
    º Your zip code   
**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that you may allow us (via your web browser settings) to place on your hard drive. Although this sounds strange at first, it is really not dangerous at all and doesn't endanger your privacy, your computer or the personal information stored there. Let's take a look at why:   
VISITORZ464MYLABTFP8HF1LNJ53SX51EL496  
www.solidsignal.com07143765322939363319322252029326235*   
What you have just seen is a typical cookie from an SolidSignal.com website. You probably have dozens of cookies on your computer just like this one, from sites you have visited. No web server on the Internet can retrieve cookie information unless they are the one that put it there. Our cookies may be tied to your personally identifiable information, however at no point do we store password information within a cookie.  
What we use cookies for is described below.  
**The Way We Use Information**  
Now that we've discussed the information we collect about you, you're probably wondering what we do with it all. Allow us to take a few moments and answer this very important question.  
**IP Addresses and Header Information**  
Although the information passed to us in an HTTP header is of a non-personal nature, many of the things we can track are vital to our ability to bring you a high quality website that you can enjoy and navigate easily.  
Some of the ways we use the information we gather from headers are:  
**·** We compile and analyze log file data to gain a cross-section representation of our visitors. This allows us to build websites that suit the needs of our customers based on their unique browser, operating system and screen resolution choices.   
**·** We compile and analyze log file data to show us where our visitors come from. This information helps our marketing department invest our time and resources in only the most cost effective and efficient advertising initiatives.   
**·** We use the visitor's IP Address as a temporary identifier to store the history of the visit and the contents of the visitors shopping cart.  
**Personal Information**  
Solid Signal uses the personal information it collects about its visitors and about people other than its visitors, in very specific and meaningful ways that directly relate to the manner in which it was received. Below are detailed the ways that we use information:  
**·** If a visitor emails us regarding an issue, our staff will reply to the email with the intention of providing the information requested by the visitor. Once the question or request for information is resolved, the visitor email will be archived for up to 1 year and then destroyed. At no time are the email addresses in this group sold, or used for any other purpose whatsoever. If that visitor were to email us and include personally identifiable information about another person, that other person's information would likewise be used for the purpose at hand and ultimately destroyed.   
**·** If a visitor fills out one of our response forms regarding a question or request for information, our staff will reply to the request via email or phone, depending on the customer's wish (as specified in the form.) Once the question or request for information is resolved, the visitor's response form data will be archived for up to 1 year and then destroyed. If a response form contains a checkbox option for inclusion in future promotional mailings, and the user hasn't opted out of the check-box, the customer's information will be logged in our promotional email database. If not, we will at no time use the customer's information for any other purpose whatsoever. For details of our policy regarding acceptable uses of visitor email addresses, please see below.  
**·** The information collected at the point of purchase from a visitor is used by us to efficiently and effectively fulfill that order to the customer. We also log the customer's acceptance of our sales terms, if applicable. Making a purchase from a Solid Signal website will cause you to receive several functional and necessary emails which are detailed below. A customer may also receive a phone call as a result of an order to verify essential information. Such as credit card billing address information used for transaction verification.  
**·** We use 3rd party service providers to administer financial transactions and shipment of purchased products. It is necessary for us to provide these companies with your personally identifiable information in order to fulfill the requested purchase and or services. These 3rd party providers are prohibited from using your personal information for any secondary purposes.

If you choose to make a payment via PayPal, please be aware that you will be brought directly to the PayPal website to conduct this transaction and any information submitted here is done so directly to PayPal and not to SolidSignal  
  
**Cookies**  
Solid Signal uses cookie technology in several ways that do not abuse the trust or confidence of our visitors. These ways are detailed as follows:   
**·** We set cookies on certain pages where we make use of JavaScript 'pop-up' windows to determine whether or not a visitor has been prompted by a particular window. This increases visitor satisfaction because it means we don't make you look at a pop-up window more than once per visit.   
**·** We set cookies to recognize a returning visitor. This allows us to maintain your individual settings, if applicable.   
  
Solid Signal does not require cookies and if you reject our cookie you may still use our site. The only drawback is that your experience will be less convenient and personalized.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site.  We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Solid Signal only and does not cover the use of cookies by any business partners.  
**Solid Signal Customer E-mail Policy**  
One of the most widely discussed facets of online privacy deals with unsolicited email messages affectionately known as SPAM. Solid Signal does not SPAM its customers and recognizes that SPAM is a harmful and unwanted nuisance. We do, however, send email messages to our customers under certain circumstances and would like to explain the rules that govern our decision to do so.   
**Email Messages Resulting From an Order**  
**·** A customer who orders product from us online (as opposed to phoning their order into our call center) will receive an email confirmation within a few moments that their order was successfully processed by our shopping cart. This additional mailing is the only way in which orders placed online and offline differ.  
**·** A customer who places an order with us is agreeing to receive a certain number of informational emails that we feel are a critical part of a confirmed order. The number of e-mails we send are the absolute minimum that we need to send to satisfy our needs, including shipping & tracking confirmation and the provision of a sales receipt to the customer.   
**·** If the customer chooses to unsubscribe they will not receive any more direct e-mails. Unless they purchase another product from us. Removal from the email mailing list can be accomplished after any mailing by following the unsubscribe instructions included with the mailing or logging into their Solid Signal Account.   
  
** Email Messages Resulting From Newsletter Sign Up**  
  
**·** When you place an order or sign up for our newsletters and special offers emails you will receive occasional emails sent by us.  You may opt-out of these optional communications at any time by accessing your account online and changing preferences or by unsubscribing directly from the email communications themselves.  We do not share your email address with any outside parties; however, we do send promotional offers on behalf of our partners.  
**Tell-A-Friend**  
**·** If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address.  We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.  Solid Signal does not store this information and the email is for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.  
**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   
**·** In many cases, we verify the accuracy of the individually identifiable information by contacting our customers and confirming the information we have after an online sale. This process covers all of our individually identifiable information that is collected and stored because all of this type of information is sales related.  
**·** We utilize SSL Encryption technology to protect your online order and personal information from theft and misuse when you are connected to our secure server. VeriSign digitally signs their secure Internet servers, so you can be sure we are who we represent ourselves to be.   
| Our 128-Bit SSL encryption certificate is provided by GeoTrust online security providers. For more information regarding the validity of our SSL certificate, you may click on the GeoTrust logo to the right |   
---|---  
**·** Our Servers are locked at all times and are only accessed by properly authorized staff.   
**·** Please be aware that certain communications, namely email and telephone conversations are not protected by SSL encryption and third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.   
**·** Although we use practices equal to or exceeding industry standard to protect your privacy, "perfect security" simply does not exist on the Internet. Personally identifiable information from your communications sent to us via an unsecured means (such as email) may be intercepted by a third party and may not remain secure.  
**Legal Disclaimer**  
**·** Please be aware that we may be required to disclose information about you to the government or third parties under certain circumstances as required by law such as to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or subpoena. We cooperate fully with all law enforcement inquiries and with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights. Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials to the extent required to comply with the law.   
**Our Employees and Your Privacy**  
Of course we realize that any policy or set of procedures is only as good as the men and women who implement it. Solid Signal has a well-trained, professional staff that is committed to your satisfaction. We recognized early how important the issue of privacy would be to our customers and implemented an employee privacy awareness program that has had great results. Each of our employees has read and fully understands the implications of this document and is committed to making our company a safe and customer-friendly place to do business.   
**External Links** ** **  
Our websites may contain links to other destinations on the World Wide Web. Please be aware that Solid Signal has not reviewed and is not responsible for the privacy practices of other companies.   
**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**  
We understand that protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.  
**Changes to this Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.  
**Miscellaneous**  
If a user chooses to submit a testimonial the following personal information will be displayed with their posting (example: first name, last initial, city and state).  We obtain our users consent prior to posting their testimonials on our site. We do this to protect your identity; however, please take care not to include any personally identifiable information within your submitted testimonial as we cannot control other’s use of this information. Please be aware that any personally identifiable information submitted within your testimonial can be viewed by other visitors to the site and used to send you unsolicited communication. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information you choose to submit within your testimonial.   
In addition to the above disclosure of policy and procedure, there are several other facts that we believe you should be aware of when evaluating our privacy policies and practices. These additional facts are:   
**        ·** Solid Signal is not part of any licensing group.  
**        ·** Solid Signal does not utilize any profile-based advertising on-site.   
**Blog and Forums Disclosure**  
If you use a bulletin board, blog, or chat room on this website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users on these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information that you choose to submit in these forums.  
**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies and practices we would truly like to hear from you. What are your concerns about privacy? What can we do to explain the issue to you better? Please direct your questions, comments and concerns to us at _[ info@SolidSignal.com](mailto:info@SolidSignal.com)._  
**How to Verify, Correct or Remove Information in Our Database**  
You can verify your inclusion in our database (or review all of your personally identifiable information that we have collected and maintain) by accessing your account online or contacting us at _[ info@SolidSignal.com](mailto:info@SolidSignal.com)._ You can correct factual inaccuracies in your personally identifiable information or make updates by editing the information in your online account or by sending us a request that credibly shows the error. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before making corrections.   
You can remove yourself from our database by contacting us with a request to do so. Your removal shall not include removal from our order database if there is an actual transaction in your name. Although we will agree to protect your personal information from future use, we cannot remove a record of a past transaction.   
** **  
**Contact us:**   
Signal Group LLC  
SolidSignal.com  
SolidSignal.tv

25225 Regency Drive  
Novi, MI 48375

1-866-374-4625
